<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Products>
  <Product>
    <id>0</id>
    <title>gh</title>
    <brand>gh</brand>
    <price>0</price>
    <quantity>0</quantity>
    <description>gh</description>
    <image>gh</image>
    <category>gh</category>
    <type>gh</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>1</id>
    <title>Apple iPhone 13 Pro</title>
    <brand>Apple</brand>
    <price>1000999</price>
    <quantity>3</quantity>
    <description>The product is refurbished, fully functional, and in excellent condition. Backed by the 90-day Amazon Renewed Guarantee. - This pre-owned product has been professionally inspected, tested and cleaned by Amazon qualified vendors. It is not certified by Apple. - This product is in "Excellent condition". The screen and body show no signs of cosmetic damage visible from 12 inches away. - This product will have a battery that exceeds 80% capacity relative to new. - Accessories may not be original, but will be compatible and fully functional. Product may come in generic box. - Product will come with a SIM removal tool, a charger and a charging cable. Headphone and SIM card are not included. - This product is eligible for a replacement or refund within 90-day of receipt if it does not work as expected. - Refurbished phones are not guaranteed to be waterproof.</description>
    <image>AppleiPhone13Pro.png</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Mobile Phones</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>2</id>
    <title>Google Pixel 6 Pro</title>
    <brand>Google</brand>
    <price>898000</price>
    <quantity>50</quantity>
    <description>Unlocked Android cell phone gives you the flexibility to change carriers and choose your own data plan[1]; the new, redesigned Pixel 6 Pro is the smartest and fastest Pixel yet[2] The powerful Google Tensor processor is the first processor designed by Google and made for Pixel; takes performance to a whole new level Advanced camera system with wide and ultrawide lenses, 4x optical zoom, and a main sensor that captures 150% more light[3] Pixel&#x2019;s Magic Eraser[4], Motion Mode, and Portrait Mode professional tools keep your photos sharp, accurate, and focused; Face Unblur can deblur a face to make it sharper[5] Pixel&#x2019;s fast charging all day battery adapts to you and saves power for apps you use the most [6,7] Keeps your phone protected with the next gen Titan M2 chip, 5 years of security updates[8], and the most hardware layers of any phone[9] New Pixel experience is more modern and intuitive, with colors that reflect your personal style; the At a Glance feature shows you the apps and info you need when you need it, like a boarding pass before a flight[10]</description>
    <image>GooglePixel6Pro.png</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Mobile Phones</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>4</id>
    <title>Apple MacBook Pro with Apple M1 Chip</title>
    <brand>Apple</brand>
    <price>66000</price>
    <quantity>2</quantity>
    <description>Color: Space Grey Size; 13-Inch Cutting-edge technology Packed with features</description>
    <image>AppleMacBookProwithAppleM1Chip.jpg</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Laptops</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>5</id>
    <title>2021 Apple MacBook Pro</title>
    <brand>Apple</brand>
    <price>44000</price>
    <quantity>3</quantity>
    <description>Apple M1 Pro or M1 Max chip for a massive leap in CPU, GPU and machine learning performance Up to 10-core CPU delivers up to 3.7x faster performance to fly through pro workflows quicker than ever Up to 32-core GPU with up to 13x faster performance for graphics-intensive apps and games 16-core Neural Engine for up to 11x faster machine learning performance Longer battery life, up to 17 hours</description>
    <image>2021AppleMacBookPro.jpg</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Laptops</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>6</id>
    <title>Lenovo IdeaPad Gaming 3 Laptop</title>
    <brand>Lenovo </brand>
    <price>20999</price>
    <quantity>9</quantity>
    <description>Lenovo IdeaPad Gaming 3 Laptop - 11th Intel Core i7-11370H, 16GB RAM, 1TB HDD + 256GB SSD, NVIDIA GTX 1650 4GB GDDR6 Graphics, 15.6" FHD 1920x1080 IPS 120Hz, 4-Zone RGB Backlit Keyboard, Dos - Black Good Quality with a high end</description>
    <image>LenovoIdeaPadGaming3Laptop.jpg</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Laptops</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>7</id>
    <title>Sony PlayStation 5 Console</title>
    <brand>Sony</brand>
    <price>16000</price>
    <quantity>3</quantity>
    <description>Sony Play Station</description>
    <image>SonyPlayStation5Console.jpg</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Consoles</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>108</id>
    <title>Adidas B 3S T SET HE9342</title>
    <brand>Adidas</brand>
    <price>662</price>
    <quantity>12</quantity>
    <description>Regular fit Tee: Crewneck 1% recycled polyester interlock Tee: Soft doubleknit back panel Moisture absorbing</description>
    <image>AdidasB3STSETHE9342.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Sportswear</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>109</id>
    <title>New Balance Cotton Front Logo</title>
    <brand>new Balance</brand>
    <price>619</price>
    <quantity>17</quantity>
    <description>100% Cotton Pull on design Made in Indonesia</description>
    <image>NewBalanceCottonFrontLogo.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Sportswear</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>110</id>
    <title>Adidas TIRO21 TK JKT</title>
    <brand>Adidas</brand>
    <price>1499</price>
    <quantity>8</quantity>
    <description>Slim fit 100% recycled polyester doubleknit Front zip pockets</description>
    <image>AdidasTIRO21TKJKT.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Sportswear</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>111</id>
    <title>Adidas EQ19 RUN</title>
    <brand>Adidas</brand>
    <price>1379</price>
    <quantity>5</quantity>
    <description>Textile upper with TPU support Highly breathable feel</description>
    <image>AdidasEQ19RUN.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Running Shoes </type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>112</id>
    <title>Skechers Mens Go Run Pulse</title>
    <brand>Skechers</brand>
    <price>700</price>
    <quantity>4</quantity>
    <description>Air-Cooled Memory Foam Lightweight and responsive ULTRA TRAIL cushioning Skechers M-Strike technology Flexible outsole Comfort Pillar Technology</description>
    <image>SkechersMensGoRun.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Running Shoes </type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>113</id>
    <title>Reebok</title>
    <brand>Reebok</brand>
    <price>2500</price>
    <quantity>3</quantity>
    <description>Reebok Shoe Soft leather upper Comfortable moulded sockliner RUNNING</description>
    <image>Reebok.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Running Shoes </type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>114</id>
    <title>3 In 1 Home Fitness Equipment</title>
    <brand>Hao Bao</brand>
    <price>145</price>
    <quantity>7</quantity>
    <description>Brand : Hao Bao Type : Training Cones Sporting Good Category : Training Equipment Are batteries needed to power the product or is this product a battery : No Is this a Dangerous Good or a Hazardous Material, Substance or Waste that is regulated for transportation, storage, and/or disposal? : No</description>
    <image>3In1HomeFitnessEquipment.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Equipment</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>115</id>
    <title>Dumbbell Set, 6 In 1 Adjustable Weights</title>
    <brand>SportQ</brand>
    <price>1500</price>
    <quantity>7</quantity>
    <description>Dumbbell Set, 6 In 1 Adjustable Weights Dumbbells Sets, Barbell Set with Connecting Rod for Adults Women Men Workout Fitness,Home Gym Exercise Training Equipment</description>
    <image>DumbbellSet,6In1AdjustableWeights.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Equipment</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>116</id>
    <title>PowerMax Fitness MFT-410</title>
    <brand>PowerMax Fitness</brand>
    <price>2800</price>
    <quantity>4</quantity>
    <description>Max User Weight: 120Kg 4 In 1 Jogger, Stepper, Twister And Push Up Bar Five Window Lcd Display Speed, Time, Distance, Calories And Heart Rate.3,Level Manual Incline For Intense Workout Max User Weight: 120Kg.4 Target Based Modes.Heart Rate Sensors On Handrail.Foldable With Manual Lock Good Quality Strong Steel Frame.Material: Steel</description>
    <image>PowerMaxFitnessMFT-410.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Equipment</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>117</id>
    <title>Smart Watch for Men</title>
    <brand>SHARAV</brand>
    <price>295</price>
    <quantity>22</quantity>
    <description>Smart Watch for Men - Fitness Watch with Heart Rate Activity Tracker Waterproof Body, Step and Calorie Counter, Blood Pressure,(20), OLED Touchscreen Watch for Men  Women - Black</description>
    <image>SmartWatchforMen.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Fitness Watches</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>118</id>
    <title>M4 Smart Band 4 Fitness Tracker</title>
    <brand>Dilo</brand>
    <price>143</price>
    <quantity>16</quantity>
    <description>Tracker Watch Sport Bracelet Heart Rate Blood Pressure Smartband Monitor Health Wristband Band Bracelet - Red</description>
    <image>M4SmartBand4FitnessTracker.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Fitness Watches</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>119</id>
    <title>Value Smash Full Screen Bluetooth</title>
    <brand>Value Smash</brand>
    <price>340</price>
    <quantity>5</quantity>
    <description>This 1.4 Inch Sensitive Full Touch Screen: Our android smartwatch use Highly sensitive capacitive full round face 1.4inch curved IPS HD touch screen display with 240 x 240 resolution. It brings you a better interactive experience, offering quick access to workout data. You can find great pleasure through smooth operational procedures, vivid information display and elegant interface. Multi-Function Mens smartwatch: Use our activity tracker to track your calories and steps, heart rate and sleep monitoring, 8 sport modes, shared GPS, remote photos, music playing, alarm clock, multi-timezone, multi-language, daylight saving time, adjust brightness, find phone and notification push including facebook, twitter, email, incoming calls, texts, etc. It has 30 Days Long Standby and Wide Compatibility with iOS and Android: Our magnetic charging cable ensures easy charging of your fitness trackers. A 1.5 hour charge gives you up to 7 days of use and 30 days standby, it can keep you organized and productive all day. Our digital watch is compatible with Bluetooth 4.0, iOS 9.0 or higher, Android 5.0 or higher Smartphones to get call, text, calendar and smartphone app notifications when your phone is nearby. Smartwatch for Men Women: Soft silicone material tape, anti-sweat matte surface treatment, ergonomic convex design and soft strap which make your smartwatch wearing more comfortable. Also, The adjustable band of the sports watches for men suitable for wrist sizes from 3.9 to 9.25 inches make it ideal for women, men and teens. P67 Swimming Waterproof Fitness Watches: IP67 water-resistant, you can wear it when washing hands, in the rain and swimming. This smartwatches can be a very good gift choice to make people live more healthy, more active and more convenient</description>
    <image>ValueSmashFullScreenBluetooth.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Fitness Watches</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>120</id>
    <title>LOOX Massage Gun</title>
    <brand>LOOX</brand>
    <price>430</price>
    <quantity>22</quantity>
    <description>It can relieve muscle stiffness and pain after exercise, and accelerate deep release of fascia gun to relieve muscle stiffness and pain. Equipped with smaller size, longer life of high-power brushless motor, in order to ensure the strong power at the same time, ensure the normal operation of the machine. Promote blood circulation, reduce muscle stiffness and soreness, improve body tissue health. In order to provide a more comfortable massage experience, we provide four matching professional massage heads for different parts, which can be replaced according to their own needs. Five speed control simple and convenient key; one button switch design, according to the long and short rhythm change function. The finger position grip of the handle fits the finger, which is safe and non slip, comfortable and effortless.</description>
    <image>LOOXMassageGun.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Supplements</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>121</id>
    <title>Non-Slip Yoga Mat</title>
    <brand>Qshop</brand>
    <price>150</price>
    <quantity>14</quantity>
    <description>Comes with a strap and bag for easy carrying and storage Made of environmentally friendly and non-toxic materials PERFECT PERFORMANCE - Professional high density yoga mat provides great support, high bounce construction Suitable for various yoga movements, Liz mat provides a comfortable experience with excellent cushioning and is suitable for all yoga levels. LIGHTWEIGHT AND EASY TO CARRY - Our yoga mat is light enough to carry to the gym or anywhere else you want with our carrying strap. Size: 183 x 61 Suitable for indoor or outdoor use, this durable yoga mat features easy to install, quick release, and most importantly, stays flat on the floor without creasing the edges.</description>
    <image>Non-SlipYogaMat.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Supplements</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>122</id>
    <title>Neocell Super Collagen</title>
    <brand>Neocell </brand>
    <price>684</price>
    <quantity>63</quantity>
    <description>Manufacturer Number : Neocell Expirable : Yes Category Type : Body  Face Suitable Skin Type : All Skin Type Texture : Powder Type : Skin Care Sets Brand : other size :200 grams</description>
    <image>NeocellSuperCollagen.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Supplements</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>123</id>
    <title>eufy Smart Scale C1</title>
    <brand>eufy </brand>
    <price>1635</price>
    <quantity>5</quantity>
    <description>eufy Smart Scale C1 with Bluetooth, Body Fat Scale, Wireless Digital Bathroom Scale, 12 Measurements, Weight/Body Fat/BMI, Fitness Body Composition Analysis, Black/White, lbs/kg, 1 Count (Pack of 1)</description>
    <image>eufySmartScale.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Scale</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>124</id>
    <title>Xiaomi Smart Weight Scale</title>
    <brand>Xiaomi</brand>
    <price>500</price>
    <quantity>24</quantity>
    <description>Weighing Scale 2 Bluetooth 5.0 Precision Fitness XMTZC04HM, White requires 3 batteries</description>
    <image>XiaomiSmartWeightScale.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Scale</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>125</id>
    <title>Xiaomi Smart Weight Scale</title>
    <brand>Xiaomi</brand>
    <price>500</price>
    <quantity>24</quantity>
    <description>Homever Kitchen Scale, 0.05oz/1g Accurate Food Scale with Multifunction, Stainless Steel Digital Kitchen Scale for Baking and Cooking, Silver</description>
    <image>XiaomiSmartWeightScale.jpg</image>
    <category>Fitness</category>
    <type>Scale</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>126</id>
    <title>Fun Paddle Toss and Catch</title>
    <brand>Xelue ff</brand>
    <price>75</price>
    <quantity>50</quantity>
    <description>he ball is manufactured from a high-grade plastic rubber and nylon. Made softer than a traditional ball to make it more risk-free and safe for every player. The catcher are made of velcro. Non-toxic materials and environmentally-friendly. Each paddle has a self-stick front surface and adjustable the back. Players simply stand a distance apart, toss the self-stick ball, and try to catch it on their self-stick paddle. The Toss and Catch game provides a great way to develop hand-eye coordination! With bright colors, the paddles and ball are easy to see.</description>
    <image>FunPaddleTossandCatch.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Toys</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>127</id>
    <title>Crocodile Dentist Bite Finger Game</title>
    <brand>Crocodile Dentist</brand>
    <price>95</price>
    <quantity>27</quantity>
    <description>Name: those trick toys biting my crocodile Size: length: 15 cm Material: ABS environmentally safe plastic (not easy to damage) Packing: packed in cartons Weight: 0.225 kg</description>
    <image>CrocodileDentistBite ingerGame.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Toys</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>128</id>
    <title>Jenga Classic Pull Stack Crash</title>
    <brand>Other</brand>
    <price>124</price>
    <quantity>33</quantity>
    <description>High quality Material Non-Toxic Environmentally Friendly Baby, ammonia free Enjoy the classic tower stacking game for kids from ages 3-93 Loads of fun for one or two players, or more. To set up the Timber Tower place three blocks per layer crosswise, includes 48 blocks for 16 layers. Includes 48 high quality wooden blocks. Wood : MDF Color : Multi Color</description>
    <image>JengaClassicPullStackCrash.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Toys</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>129</id>
    <title>Logitech Driving Force</title>
    <brand>Logitech</brand>
    <price>11000</price>
    <quantity>34</quantity>
    <description>Racing Wheel for PS4 PS3 and PC Dual-Motor Force Feedback Helical Gearing With Anti-Backlash Responsive Floor Pedal Unit</description>
    <image>ogitechDrivingForce.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Video Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>130</id>
    <title>Handheld Game Console</title>
    <brand>Others</brand>
    <price>2280</price>
    <quantity>6</quantity>
    <description>Platform : PlayStation Portable Hard Disk Capacity : 80 GB Brand : Other</description>
    <image>HandheldGameConsole.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Video Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>131</id>
    <title>Mocute 058</title>
    <brand>Mocute</brand>
    <price>194</price>
    <quantity>4</quantity>
    <description>Mocute 058 Wireless Bluetooth Gamepad Gaming Controller Telescopic Joystick for Android Phone PUBG Game Brand: Mocute Compatible with: Multi Accessory Type: Smart Phone Gaming Controller</description>
    <image>Mocute058WirelessBluetoothGamepad.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Video Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>132</id>
    <title>Baby Toys</title>
    <brand>HappyToys</brand>
    <price>125</price>
    <quantity>9</quantity>
    <description>Baby Toys Stacking Rainbow Duck Tower Ring Toys For Kids Children</description>
    <image>BabyToys.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Baby Friendly</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>133</id>
    <title>Foldable Baby Kids</title>
    <brand>Others</brand>
    <price>30</price>
    <quantity>4</quantity>
    <description>Targeted Group : Unisex Brand : Other Type : Portable Beds  Playard BABY KIDS SAFETY PROTECTION CARE PLAYPEN TENT CRAWLING GAME FOLDING FENCE TOYS FENCING PLAY HOUSE INDOOR OUTDOOR FOR CHILDREN QUANTITY: 1 * BABY PLAYPEN MATERIAL: ABS  NYLON  OXFORD CLOTH COLOR: PINK FOR 0 TO 4 YEARS OLD BABIES PLAY AREA: 10 sq. ft</description>
    <image>FoldableBabyKids.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Baby Friendly</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>134</id>
    <title>Wooden Musical Toy</title>
    <brand>Generic</brand>
    <price>90</price>
    <quantity>6</quantity>
    <description>Brand : Other Toy Category : Light, Sound  Music Toys Targeted Group : Unisex Age : All Ages Manufacturer Recommended Age : 3 Years  Above Are batteries needed to power the product or is this product a battery : No Is this a Dangerous Good or a Hazardous Material, Substance or Waste that is regulated for transportation, storage, and/or disposal? : No</description>
    <image>WoodenMusicalToy.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Baby Friendly</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>135</id>
    <title>Monopoly</title>
    <brand>Others</brand>
    <price>150</price>
    <quantity>6</quantity>
    <description>Toy Category: Board and Card Games Targeted Group: Unisex Seamless functionality Packed with features</description>
    <image>Monopoly.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Board Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>136</id>
    <title>Jumbo Sequence</title>
    <brand>Others</brand>
    <price>220</price>
    <quantity>19</quantity>
    <description>Jumbo Sequence Board and Card Games Box Edition with Party Funny Toy - Family Game</description>
    <image>JumboSequence.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Board Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>137</id>
    <title>Jumanji The Game</title>
    <brand>Spin Master Games</brand>
    <price>520</price>
    <quantity>5</quantity>
    <description>The Game, The Classic Scary Adventure Family Board Game Based on the Action-Comedy Movie, for Kids and Adults Ages 8  up</description>
    <image>Jumanji.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Board Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>138</id>
    <title>Monopoly Deal Card Game</title>
    <brand>Others</brand>
    <price>50</price>
    <quantity>3</quantity>
    <description>Brand : Other Toy Category : Board  Card Games Targeted Group : Unisex Manufacturer Recommended Age : 10 Years  Above Age : 10 Years  Above</description>
    <image>MonopolyDealCardGame.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Card Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>139</id>
    <title>UNO Card Game</title>
    <brand>Mattel</brand>
    <price>40</price>
    <quantity>4</quantity>
    <description>Toy Category : Collection Cards Targeted Group : Unisex Manufacturer Recommended Age : 6 Years  Above Age : 6 Years  Above Brand : Mattel Made in USA</description>
    <image>UNOCardGame.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Card Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>140</id>
    <title>CODENAMES Party Card Game</title>
    <brand>PoRo</brand>
    <price>295</price>
    <quantity>7</quantity>
    <description>Brand : PoRo Toy Category : Board  Card Games Targeted Group : Unisex Age : All Ages Recommended Age : 12 Years  Above</description>
    <image>CODENAMESPartyCardGame.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Card Games</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>141</id>
    <title>Rainbowtoy Foam</title>
    <brand>Rainbowtoy </brand>
    <price>170</price>
    <quantity>9</quantity>
    <description>Brand: Rainbowtoy Product weight: 3 kg Targeted Group: Unisex Age: All Ages Outdoor Play Activities: Outdoor Activities and Games Recommended Age: All Ages Are batteries needed to power the product or is this product a battery: No Is this a Dangerous Good or a Hazardous Material, Substance or Waste that is regulated for transportation, storage, and/or disposal: No</description>
    <image>RainbowtoyFoam.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Puzzles</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>142</id>
    <title>Mountain idyll</title>
    <brand>trefl</brand>
    <price>275</price>
    <quantity>6</quantity>
    <description>Puzzle consisting of 500 pieces with a view of the house in the mountains. After laying, a 580 x 340mm picture will be created High quality, color saturation and safe stacking is provided by calendared, reflective paper coated with ecological food paints It strengthens interpersonal ties Provides relaxation Enhances power of observation, concentration and precision</description>
    <image>Mountainidyll.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Puzzles</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>143</id>
    <title>Monsters University </title>
    <brand>CuteCat</brand>
    <price>150</price>
    <quantity>7</quantity>
    <description>Monsters University - 300 PCS</description>
    <image>MonstersUniversity.jpg</image>
    <category>Toys and Games</category>
    <type>Puzzles</type>
  </Product>
</Products>
