<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Products>
  <Product>
    <id>1</id>
    <title>Apple iPhone 13 Pro</title>
    <brand>Apple</brand>
    <price>1000999</price>
    <quantity>3</quantity>
    <description>The product is refurbished, fully functional, and in excellent condition. Backed by the 90-day Amazon Renewed Guarantee. - This pre-owned product has been professionally inspected, tested and cleaned by Amazon qualified vendors. It is not certified by Apple. - This product is in "Excellent condition". The screen and body show no signs of cosmetic damage visible from 12 inches away. - This product will have a battery that exceeds 80% capacity relative to new. - Accessories may not be original, but will be compatible and fully functional. Product may come in generic box. - Product will come with a SIM removal tool, a charger and a charging cable. Headphone and SIM card are not included. - This product is eligible for a replacement or refund within 90-day of receipt if it does not work as expected. - Refurbished phones are not guaranteed to be waterproof.</description>
    <image>AppleiPhone13Pro.png</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Mobile Phones</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>2</id>
    <title>Google Pixel 6 Pro</title>
    <brand>Google</brand>
    <price>898000</price>
    <quantity>50</quantity>
    <description>Unlocked Android cell phone gives you the flexibility to change carriers and choose your own data plan[1]; the new, redesigned Pixel 6 Pro is the smartest and fastest Pixel yet[2] The powerful Google Tensor processor is the first processor designed by Google and made for Pixel; takes performance to a whole new level Advanced camera system with wide and ultrawide lenses, 4x optical zoom, and a main sensor that captures 150% more light[3] Pixel&#x2019;s Magic Eraser[4], Motion Mode, and Portrait Mode professional tools keep your photos sharp, accurate, and focused; Face Unblur can deblur a face to make it sharper[5] Pixel&#x2019;s fast charging all day battery adapts to you and saves power for apps you use the most [6,7] Keeps your phone protected with the next gen Titan M2 chip, 5 years of security updates[8], and the most hardware layers of any phone[9] New Pixel experience is more modern and intuitive, with colors that reflect your personal style; the At a Glance feature shows you the apps and info you need when you need it, like a boarding pass before a flight[10]</description>
    <image>GooglePixel6Pro.png</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Mobile Phones</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>4</id>
    <title>Apple MacBook Pro with Apple M1 Chip</title>
    <brand>Apple</brand>
    <price>66000</price>
    <quantity>2</quantity>
    <description>Color: Space Grey Size; 13-Inch Cutting-edge technology Packed with features</description>
    <image>AppleMacBookProwithAppleM1Chip.jpg</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Laptops</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>5</id>
    <title>2021 Apple MacBook Pro</title>
    <brand>Apple</brand>
    <price>44000</price>
    <quantity>3</quantity>
    <description>Apple M1 Pro or M1 Max chip for a massive leap in CPU, GPU and machine learning performance Up to 10-core CPU delivers up to 3.7x faster performance to fly through pro workflows quicker than ever Up to 32-core GPU with up to 13x faster performance for graphics-intensive apps and games 16-core Neural Engine for up to 11x faster machine learning performance Longer battery life, up to 17 hours</description>
    <image>2021AppleMacBookPro.jpg</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Laptops</type>
  </Product>
  <Product>
    <id>6</id>
    <title>Lenovo IdeaPad Gaming 3 Laptop</title>
    <brand>Lenovo </brand>
    <price>20999</price>
    <quantity>9</quantity>
    <description>Lenovo IdeaPad Gaming 3 Laptop - 11th Intel Core i7-11370H, 16GB RAM, 1TB HDD + 256GB SSD, NVIDIA GTX 1650 4GB GDDR6 Graphics, 15.6" FHD 1920x1080 IPS 120Hz, 4-Zone RGB Backlit Keyboard, Dos - Black Good Quality with a high end</description>
    <image>LenovoIdeaPadGaming3Laptop.jpg</image>
    <category>Electronics</category>
    <type>Laptops</type>
  </Product>
</Products>
